Diana Davies Papers, 1960s-1996 (ongoing)
Sophia Smith Collection, Smith College
- Northampton State Hospital Squat and Squatters Housing Rights Material
  - The squatters' house at 251 Pleasant St., Northampton-10 or so people lived here and ran the building which had been abandoned, 1977 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - "The Not-Squat" - a former squat, now owned by the ex-squatters. Philadelphia, 1995 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Miscellaneous flyers, clippings, pamphlets - Western Mass squatters and homelessness (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Miscellaneous flyers, clippings, on Western Mass squatters shelters, homelessness (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - A squatters' zine from Philadelphia--"Squat Beautiful", 1995 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Miscellaneous flyers, clippings, pamphlets - US and world wide squatters, squats, and homelessness (Box 13, Folder 14)
- Welfare Rights and Economic Human Rights Struggle
  - "Stop Welfare Reform" 1998 demo. Various groups (AFSC, Pioneer Valley Welfare Rights Coalition, etc.), Northampton, MA (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - "Welfare Moms" purple heart badge and info, Western Mass., 1999 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Arise for Social Justice (ARISE) of Springfield, Mass.- an intro, 1990s- (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Arise - economic human rights demo, 1998. Springfield, Mass and rally, march workers (Box 14, Folder 4-6)
  - (Springfield, Mass., to NYC) Kensington Welfare Rights Union (KWRU) and Arise - bus caravan, march on the UN and all day testimony and cultural event at the UN church center, 1998 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - KWRU and Arise - march on the UN, NYC, cont., workers, speakers, etc., 1998 (Box 14, Folder 8-12)
  - Beulah Sanders of the National Welfare Rights Organization, 1970, at a peace march, NYC (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Child at a civil rights rally - "Welfare Rights Now!" button on coat, NYC, 1968 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Vietnam Vet (ex-medic), at a huge anti-war rally, Washington D.C., has "Welfare Rights Now!" button on jacket, 1971 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Info, flyers, statistics, etc. from welfare rights groups and events in this series (Box 14, Folder 16)
- Poor People's Campaign, 1968
  - In "tent city," Washington D.C. community (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Organizing march, Northeast caravan. Queens to NYC (Manhattan) and rally in Central Park (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - On-the-road. Various bus caravans - Northeast cities to Washington D.C., NY, NJ, Baltimore, Delaware, D.C. (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Tent city, Washington D.C. (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Miscellaneous prints (Box 15, Folder 5)
- Civil Rights Movement and African-American History
  - Portraits, civil rights movement activists (includes Fannie Lou Hamer, Coretta Scott King, Afeni Shakur, Angela Yvonne Davis, Ella Baker, Bernice Johnson Reagon) (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Marches and demonstrations, miscellaneous prints, and some cross-referenced material (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Stokely Carmichael - Kwame Toure, speaks in honor of Malcolm X, Audubon Ballroom, NYC, 1966 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Mississippi cops and people, waiting for civil rights march, Marks, Mississippi, 1968 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Civil rights and poor people's organizing, near Baltimore, MD, James Orange, speaker, 1968 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Harlem marches with the Selma (Alabama) civil rights movement, NYC, 1965 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Harlem, NYC: street scenes, Apollo theatre, Frederic Douglass Bookstore, etc., 1965 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - "Let there be peace on earth for all black men" graffiti, and a woman's face, subway, NYC, 1965 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Women with "Black is beautiful" etc. sign, NYC; and "Welcome to Mississippi" sign from bus window, 1968 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Queen Mother Moore, leader in African-American rights and cultural history movement, NYC; parade in memory of Malcolm X, and black Muslims, 1966 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - "Black Power" demo and civil rights march and poor people's rights organizing, Mississippi, 1968 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Black Panther Party (NY) and "Free the Panther 21" demo at criminal court building, NYC, Dec. 1969 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Black Panther Party (NY) and "Free the Panther 21" rally at Columbia Univ., NYC, 1970 (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - March in memory of Martin Luther King Jr., NYC, to city hall, 1968 (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - People's rally in memory of Martin Luther King Jr., NYC (includes Ossie Davis, Pete Seeger, Benjamin Spock), 1968 (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - Memorial service/rallies for Martin Luther King Jr. and civil rights and poor people's organizing, Lorraine Motel and Masonic Temple, Memphis, 1968 (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - NYC - official Government rally in memory of Martin Luther King Jr., Central Park, 1968 (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - Published material and miscellaneous printed matter on civil rights movement (Box 16, Folder 18)
- People's Struggles: The State of Society and the World
  - The Biafran War: Photos from the war zone; West Africa; refugees, refugee camps, bombing the targets, men with guns, relief work, etc., 1969 and 1970 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Buffalo Creek Dam Disaster: West Virginia: Kady's text and DJD photos, 1973 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Veterans in the U.S.,, miscellaneous situations, various dates (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Native-American Rights Movement
    - Lakotak ("Sioux") women with "Indian Power" sign, Washington D.C., 1968 (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - Protest at the Bureau of Indian Affairs (BIA), Washington D.C., 1968 (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - Lakotas ("Sioux") at a massive anti-war march, NYC, 1967 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Student Protests: Columbia Univ., CCNY/CUNY, 1960s (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Aging, Old age, Very-old people
    - "Thrift shop to benefit Armenian old age home" and portraits (of various cross-referenced subjects) (Box 17, Folder 8)
    - A nursing home in NJ, 1960s (location, by agreement, not to be revealed) (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Children: Youngish people, miscellaneous environments, activities, b&w, cross- referenced material, slides (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - US Culture - Non-culture: the bingo hall, 1993 and middle/muddle American culture (?) (non-culture), Coastal Maine (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Hate Crimes: Fighting hate crimes in Greenfield, Mass. - local people protest the defacing of a Synagogue, 1994 - "Never Again" (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - The Human Rights Movement
    - American Sosa, Rigoberta Menchu, Dom Helder, and others (cross-referenced material also), 1970s on (Box 17, Folder 13)
    - Human rights activists (includes Danilo Docci (Italy) and Joan Baez (US) speaking on non-violent organizing of communities, 1971 (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - Irish Nationalism: "England out of Ireland" in St. Patrick's Day parade, NYC, 1972 (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - "The Hippies" Series
    - Miscellaneous portraits, 1960s, NYC and San Francisco drummers, dancers, flowers, painted cars and bodies, etc. Color slides and b&w (Box 17, Folder 16)
    - Hippies, psychedelic cultural event (includes Timothy Leary, Allen Ginsberg, others) Theatre, NYC, 1966 (Box 17, Folder 17)
    - Hippie "be-in" gathering, Central Park, NY, 1968 (Box 17, Folder 18)
    - Alternative community church service, Glide Memorial Church, 1967, San Francisco (Box 17, Folder 19)
  - Politicians and Politics
    - Shirley Chisholm, Jimmy Breslin, Bella Abzug, Ted Kennedy, John Lindsay, various dates, locals, NYC, 1960s-70s (Box 17, Folder 20)
    - Robert Kennedy, Eugene McCarthy, Jesse Jackson - all 1968 (Box 17, Folder 21)
  - Gun Control - Gun Violence: ban - hand guns movement. Rally and memorial of empty (1000) pairs of shoes of those killed by hand guns. Springfield, MA, 1998 (Box 17, Folder 22)
  - The Right Wing
    - "God, guns, guts made America, etc." - bumper sticker on pickup. Old veteran, Memorial Day, bingo hall, 1993, Coastal Maine (Box 17, Folder 23)
    - Miscellaneous color slides - hard hats, flags, National Rifle Association decal in car window, etc. (Box 17, Folder 24)
    - Pro-war faction and various racist and right-wing groups picket against a peace march, NYC, 1967 (Box 17, Folder 25)
    - Pro-war in Vietnam march William F. Buckley and a variety of blockheads, 1965, NYC (Box 17, Folder 26)
    - Neo-Nazi, Washington D.C., 1960s (Box 17, Folder 27)
    - Right-wing woman with flags. Pro-war march, 1966, NY (Box 17, Folder 28)
    - Miscellaneous prints and subjects. Woman with "Bomb Hanoi" sign, etc. and info (Box 17, Folder 29)
    - Swastika graffiti on a dumpster, NYC. Lower East side, 1995 (Box 17, Folder 30)
- Common Stock - a workers' collective
  - Common Stock restaurant and workers, Brookline, Mass. (includes Beatrice Hawley, Constance "Connie" Trowbridge, Kate Albrecht) (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Building the space --Women Working! (includes Gene -woman- Albrecht, Matt Albrecht), 1978-80 (Box 18)
  - Café performance by Joanie Schwartz - folksinger; Nancy Moniz - community activist, artist, and co-worker (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Lisa Pontoppidan - co-worker, musician, filmmaker and activist (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Co-workers working in kitchen and restaurant (includes Jill Rosencrantz - harpist and cook; Jeffrey Comer - Boston gay rights activist and community organizer) (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Co-workers in kitchen and restaurant (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Info, posters, leaflets, letters, recipes (Box 18, Folder 6)
- Labor History
  - Abandoned factory and rubble, Holyoke, Mass. --"No bread and no roses either…" (includes Kady exploring in rubble), 1995 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Miscellaneous color and b&w and cross-referenced material, includes graffiti and "Justice for Janitors" jacket logo (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Several examples of IWW graffiti, various locations NYC, 1995 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - IWW printed matter, photos, designs, silkscreen by DJD, songbook, Diana's wobbly papers (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Photos, info, designs - published material by DJD for various labor organizations (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Union photos and statement from Frank Gough - Gandy Dancer (railroad track layer), riveter, high-iron worker, union organizer - DJD's grandfather, early 1900s (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Working women's songbook, copy of book by Evelyn Alloy - New England Free Press, 1976 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - UFW - United Farm Workers
    - United Farm Workers on the road, 1973 (includes Dolores Huerta, Cesar Chavez) (Box 18, Folder 14)
    - UFW picket at Bread and Circus, Hadley, MA. UFW speaking out at Smith College (includes SLAC - Student Labor Action Coalition and Nosotras - Smith College organizations; Daisy Rooks and Gretchen Purser, labor organizers), 1998 (Box 18, Folder 15)
    - UFW benefit concert program (DJD worked on project and concert), 1976 (Box 18, Folder 16)
    - UFW - grape strike support demo, NYC, 1968 (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - Photos and published info on Feigel Yudin- textile worker, labor organizer from the early 1900s on, 1970s (Box 18, Folder 18)
  - Work - a zine by DJD, 1998 (Box 18, Folder 19)
- Prison Issues and Prisoner's Rights
  - Miscellaneous: includes cross-referenced material, "Free Huey" graffiti, circa 1970 (Box 18, Folder 20)
  - NYC: Women's prison vigils and prisoner waving at demonstrators, NYC, 1969 and 1970 (Box 18)
  - Cops in various locations (Box 18)
  - Afeni Shakur, Black Panther Party member, speaking at a "Free the Panther 21" rally, NYC, 1970 (Box 18, Folder 21)
  - Man harassed by cop in NY subway, 1980s (Box 18, Folder 22)
  - Margaret Holt
    - At a "US out of Latin America" and "CIA off campus (UMass)" demo, Northampton, Mass., 1987 (Box 18, Folder 23)
    - "Free Mumia" (Abu-Jamal) vigils (several) Amherst, Mass. (includes Kady, Margaret Holt, Frances Crowe, Anna Megyesi (AFSC), others), 1995 (Box 18, Folder 24)
    - Social Justice activist at a party for her (includes, Kady, Jeanie Maland, Shanta Rao, others), 1995 (Box 18, Folder 25)
    - Correspondence from and flyers from, sent to DJD (Box 18, Folder 26)
  - Frances Crowe
    - Photos and drawing, miscellaneous papers and cross-referenced material (Box 18, Folder 27)
    - Mass protest to support and free Mumia Abu-Jamal and to protest "the contract on America," Burlington, VT (includes Kady), 1995 (Box 18, Folder 28)
    - Jeanine Maland and Kady - design, make, use a huge, street wide banner "Free Mumia," Amherst, Mass., and Philadelphia, PA,1995 (Box 18, Folder 29)
    - Prisoners' rights demo and vigil. State house, Boston. Protesting Forced relocation of Massachusetts prisoners to Texas and the Walpole prison lockdown (includes - Kady, Jeanine Maland, David Kastor - prisoners rights activists), 1998 (Box 18, Folder 30)
    - "Stop Police Brutality" event - theatre vigil, march to police station. Amherst, MA, 1995 (Box 18, Folder 31)
    - Boston/Eastern Mass prison walk - Norfolk to Walpole prisons (includes Kady), 1996 (Box 18, Folder 32)
    - "No Justice!" graffiti on Hampshire County Courthouse, Northampton, MA and "Skateboarding is not a crime" graffiti on street sign, 1994 (Box 18, Folder 33)
    - "Mothers in prison/children in crisis" campaign-- info, theatre, speakers, first churches, Northampton, MA, 1998 (Box 18, Folder 34)
    - Published material and printed matter on prison issues (Box 18, Folder 35)
- Theatre and Public Art
  - The Theatre Book (from a series of traveling notebooks) and Info, intro, how to use this… (Box 19, Folder 0)
  - The Living Theatre, Theatre of the Angry Arts, Bread and Puppet Theater, El Teatro Campesino, Pageant Players, It's All Right to be a Woman Theatre, How to Make a Woman Theatre, The Gargoyles Theatre Event, Carol "Kali" Grosberg - Theatre woman and "Apple, the cat", the San Francisco Mime Troupe (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Radical Arts Theater (RAT), poster The War Machine. Play by DJD and photos from show, flywheel community arts space theatre events (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - The Lockup -Lockdown Prison Theatre piece 1, 1997. The Hat Caper by Kady, Pat, Diana. "Big Eyes/Bug Eyes" strange Theatre thing, State Hospital Squatters Theatre (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - "Emily the Cow" and "The Fool Who Lost Her Sense of Humour" theatre pieces by DJD and flyer from Flywheel performance and "I Hate to see the Flowers Go" by DJD (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Anna's Story" theatre piece by DJD - part performed at "Crank-It-Out," Thornes Market. Crank-It-Out flyers and photos, "Bring on the Dancing Girls" silkscreen design. Handouts for "weeds" and "Suspicious Activities" street improv dance and theatre group, folk dancers, Cuba. "The Funeral Procession for Public Art" theatre piece by DJD, "Landmines not Lunches" theatre piece by DJD. "Blood Money" from anti-world trade org., theatre piece - DJD as "Global CEO from the World Greed Org (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - "Theatre of the 6 Dragons," article by Kady and photos by DJD. "Street Artists' Guild" (1990s Boston) info and photos of Stephen Baird, founder. Kady's "Trouser Design" pocket blueprint - good for travelers, clowns, performers (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Guerrilla Girls, Neil Alan "Mr N.K. Lean Young's "Movie Shoot," Smoddy Puppet Theatre Company" flyers and photos. "Nick and Sam" Street Theatre boys, 1994 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Silver Fist or Justice Theatre, "Clowns - Against - Nukes," Street Theatre and Rte. 2 Anti-Nuke Waste Theatre parade. Waffles-the-clown, Colrain, MA; R.A.Y., Columbus Day Street Theatre protest, Western Mass, 1996 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - "National Day Against Police Brutality" theatre event and script. "Living Wage and Economic Human Rights" day street theatre and "Not-so-funny Money," R.A.Y. "Uncommon Carnival" info and flyers, 1996 and 1997. Mary Weaver's "Mythweavers' Theatre" parade, Coastal Maine, 1993 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Production material, photos, script samples, photos of company, tickets, etc. from "The Witch Papers" a collage-play by DJD, 1980. Touring show by Big Hags Theatre Company (includes - Susie Chancey, Hillary Kay, Pat Styer, DJD, Kate O'Connell, Beatrice Hawley, Nan H. Wasburn, Jamie Cancey, Michelle Baxter, Michelle Gabow) (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - "Sankofa" People's Multi-cultural arts festival, 1993, Maine: dancers, drummers, kids w/ makeup-paint and streamers, anti-beauty contest theatre and demo, 1974, NY state. Clowns, miscellaneous (including DJD, Ringling Bros. - Barnum and Bailey, Laurie Krauth, Sherry Mestel). Old Vaudeville Theatre building and props, Greenfield, MA, 1993. Circus Smirkus, on tour, 1994 (includes Molly Pelley, clown) (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Pat Styer's Character, 1995. "Clara Audience" Northampton, MA. Rovin Theatre person. Linda Garson - Smith actor, "Belfast Maskers Theatre" 1993, Maine. Belfaast Maskers Theatre - various productions, 1990's, Fertile Mind Kids' Makeup and face painting workshop, 1993, Maine. Prisoners' Rights and Economic Justice Theatre Production at "Mothers in Prison Children in Crisis" program, Northampton, MA, 1998. Kids Dancing, various locations. "Trevor - the Games Man" 1994, Western Mass.,A hippie woman, dancing, 1966, NY. Drawings by DJD. Street theatre and man on unicycle, 1971, Lower East side. Felicia Thomas, court jester and human rights activist, Maine, 1993. Felicia's cat (Whoops - kitten) 1993 (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Bern Porter's 80th Birthday Celebration (1991), Coastal Maine - various theatre events, parades. Imogene - theatre woman, dancer, choreographer and gay bar worker, 1970, NYC. Dancer in fountain, Lincoln Center, NY, 196_, "Revolution, Make it in Mass" graffiti, Western Mass, 1987. The dog - design by Kady - prop, scenery, a mask: multi- purpose thing 1990s. Miscellaneous graffiti and chalk designs, various location, dates. "Hoopoe the clowne" - Chris Yerlig - mime, clown, actor, Western Mass, 1990s. "The Crazy Theatre Piece," Western Mass, RR bridge. Street theatre parade, Lower East side, 1960s. Boy watching outdoor theatre from tree, 1960s, NY state. Program, flyers, photos from the ten-dollar Movie Co… (includes Jane Picard, Filmmaker, theatre woman; Pat Styer, theatre woman and play producer) working out of Boston area, 1980s. The Mysterious clown and friends: Meredith of the Iguana Son performance and Artspace, Maine. People from an all-night traveling theatre group (all friends with Meredith) Coastal Maine, 1993. Puppets and theatre by Michelle Wilde, assisted by Kay Halm, from The "BLO - Boobie Liberation Organization," 1999, Western Mass, flyer * news clipping about street theatre by fired Iron Horse Musician Hall employees, 1997, Western Mass (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - Info, Intro, how to use this (Box 20, Folder 0)
  - Graffiti and More
    - Miscellaneous theatre color slides and b&w cross-referenced material (includes street theatre, graffiti) (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - Animal chalk drawings - graffiti in Pulaski park and miscellaneous graffiti on buildings, Northampton, MA (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - "Nick and Sam" - street theatre boys and graffiti, miscellaneous (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - "Revolution - make it happen in Mass" 1987, Northampton RR trestle (color slide) (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - Bicycle mural, Houston St., NYC, 1995 (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - "Northampton Needs a Community Center" by DJD, 1997 Theatre and Public Art (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Festivals
    - Little girl and streamers at street theatre and community festival, 1993. Maine and dancers, drumming, face painting (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - The Big Tent and street festival, 1993, Belfast, Maine. 2 older women participants (Box 20, Folder 8)
    - Little girl with bicycles - at a street theatre and community festival, Maine, 1993 (Box 20, Folder 9)
    - Street festival of San Gennaro "Little Italy," NYC, 1965 (Box 20, Folder 10)
    - Street theatre - Man on a unicycle and installation "Hand on Alarm" Lower East side, NY, 1971 (Box 20, Folder 11)
    - "The Sweet Shop Flower Folk" with Fafnir, Neil N.K. Lean Young, Susanna, and Amie - The Bearded Lady, 1999 at "Sweeties Candy Store," Northampton, MA (Box 20, Folder 12)
    - "The Crazy Theatre Piece" with Kady, Pat Styer, Diana Davies, Northampton, Mass., 1994 (Box 20, Folder 13)
    - "The Hat Caper" with Kady, Pat, Diana 1994. Northampton, MA (Box 20, Folder 14)
    - "Big Eyes - Bug Eyes" - the Strange Eyes theatre thing, 1987, with Kady, Pat, Diana. Western Mass (Box 20, Folder 15)
    - Kady in the Flea Market Mirror, 1996, the Dead Mall, Hadley, MA, "Make a Portable Funhouse" and flea market participants (Box 20, Folder 16)
    - Kady - street theatre - hands, foot, and sidewalk sgraffito, 1971, NYC (Box 20, Folder 17)
    - The Living theatre - street entrance to performance space. 14th St., NYC, 1965 -color slides (Box 20, Folder 18)
    - El Teatro Campesino - (The Farm workers' Theatre) on tour in 1967 (includes Luis Valdez, playwright and founder) (Box 20, Folder 19)
    - The Pageant Players, NYC, late 1960s. Susie and Rob, company members (Box 20, Folder 20)
    - The Pageant Players, NYC, 1960s. Street theater performances, audiences (Box 20, Folder 21)
    - "We Regret to Inform you…" - Anti war play, 1966 (?), The Pageant Players (Box 20, Folder 22)
    - Poster and 8x10 neg. for poster print by DJD for Theatre of the Angry Arts, 1967, NYC (Box 20, Folder 23)
    - Theatre of the 6 Dragons, 1971, Washington D.C
      - Daytime theatre piece, in fountain (Box 20, Folder 24)
      - Nighttime theatre piece and "How We Painted Pennsylvania Ave.with the Theater of the 6 Dragons" (includes Kady Burns draft card). "Gay May Day" and Kady with "Beware the Lavender Menace" signs, gay theatre (Box 20, Folder 25)
    - The Bread and Puppet Theater
      - April 1971, Washington D.C., huge peace march (includes Peter Schumann, founder - director; Amy and Andy Trompetter, actors) (Box 20, Folder 26)
      - "The Bach Cantata" NYC, 1960s at The Village Theatre (Box 20, Folder 27)
      - In protest at St. Patrick's Cathedral, NYC (anti-war street theatre) (Box 20, Folder 28)
      - With huge puppets at huge anti-war march, 1966, NYC (includes Peter Schumann) (Box 20, Folder 29)
      - On tour - at the Newport Folk Festival, Newport, RI, 1967 (Box 20, Folder 30)
      - On tour, 1968, at the Newport Folk Festival - little girl with large horn (Box 20, Folder 31)
      - War tax resistance day at the Greenfield, Mass., Post office. 15 April, 1998 (Box 20, Folder 32)
      - On tour, Burlington, VT, 1996. At huge rally, protest march "Against the Contract on America" and to "Free Mumia Abu-Jamal" (Box 20, Folder 33)
    - Ridiculous Theatrical Co., 1971, NYC (includes Charles Ludlam - well known "gay" playwright, founder, director, playwright; Lee Stone - poet and actors) (Box 20, Folder 34)
    - "Death of Gargoyles" street and storefront performance, 1970, NYC (includes Jane Lourie, filmmaker; Michaela Griffo, artist; little girl with flowers) (Box 20, Folder 35)
    - Man dancing in fountain at Lincoln Center, NYC, 1966 (Box 20, Folder 36)
    - Underground theatre and nightlife, 1970. "Washington Square Theatre Co." (includes Imogene, Dancer, choreographer, theatre woman, dancers) (Box 20, Folder 37)
    - "It's All Right to be a Woman Theatre Co." at SUNY, NY State. Women's conference - performance 1973 (Box 20, Folder 38)
    - "How to Make a Woman Theatre Co." Judson Memorial Church, NYC, 1969 (Box 20, Folder 39)
    - Theatre women and theatre girls, Boston Women's theatre festival, 1980 - (includes Lynn Conroy, Melanie Conroy, Cherie Jimenez, Noelle Jimenez - mother-daughter theatre people) (Box 20, Folder 40)
    - Big Hags Theatre Company, Jamaica Plains, MA, 1983 (includes Susie Chancey, Kate O'Connell, Jane Picard, Ellen Sperling) (Box 20, Folder 41)
    - Big Hags Theatre Co. on tour, 1980, Forestburgh, NY (includes Pat Styer, Susie Chancey, Jane Picard) (Box 20, Folder 42)
    - Pat Styer of big Hags Theatre Co. in Provincetown, MA, 1980 (Box 20, Folder 43)
    - Theatre to "Stop the Shipment of Yankee Rowe Nuke Plant Waste" 1996 - theatre and procession up Rte. 2 (includes Kady) (Box 20, Folder 44)